Back to the time when I used to feel your hand in mine
曾经掌心感受到你的温度
Tiniest tenderness might it melt the ice into tears
微暖 能否融化眼中的坚冰？
Far from the world that still makes both of my eyes blurred
早已远去的时间仍时时令人欲泣
Not a word could I say to wake up a dreamer
我无法出言将梦惊醒
Call out my name when you see the tide turn me away
潮汐流转之时 请将我呼唤
Long ago buried heart
久被埋葬的内心
Right away torn apart
在此刻撕碎
So it hurts how it lasts
如此的疼痛要如何持续
Till I draw one more last final breath
直到最后一丝吐息
Where to go when to come
人们去往何方 何时归来
Across a land bare and dark
在这荒芜黑暗的大地
May it be the one for all
仅愿此间唯一
Burning the horizon out into none
燃尽一切隔阂
Once in a while let my shadow stand by your side
让我的身影偶伴你身旁
Filling the emptiness of your mind then disappear
填补你意识的空洞 随即消失
Dreams can be real when a soul is armored in steel
当灵魂披巾戴甲 梦想便成真
No more fear of right or wrong embraced under my shield
无需再恐惧是非 任我包容与守护
Call out my name when you see the tide turn me away
潮汐流转之时 请将我呼唤
Long ago buried heart
久被埋的内心
Right away torn apart
在此刻撕碎
So it hurts how it lasts
如此的疼痛要如何持续
Till I draw one more last final breath
直到最后一丝吐息
Where to go when to come
人们去往何方 何时归来
Across a land bare and dark
在这荒芜黑暗的大地
May it be the one for all
仅愿此间唯一
Burning the horizon out into none
燃尽一切隔阂